kar do
[music]
that welcome to icicibank.com
investor help reduce in this video you will learn how to buy
stocks nicibank.com
electronic ic 179 username
password and dist your pan card
number is on the left side of the page and ₹1000
note withdraw from bank balance equity
shares sor options left side panel celebs
kim love you can choose
reproductive start
investing in thanks buy and flexis
in kest but this buy stocks with depression
after payment 20 stocks in the great you
demat account in plus two days after that you can see them
anytime you want to bring in a lot
of problems and delivery of
bsc and msc click on you will be
available for stock company infosys company ne
you can also select options to get current
price details
that last rate price ya jude logo de open
previous closing price in all the best
fight with girls top girls top entry
quantity use calculator  Calculate Number of
Toxic Select The Amazing Owaisi for
Tuesday Next This Select You All the
Best All Select Market Subscribe and
Subscribe the Channel Please subscribe
and subscribe the
Now You are all set to execute
straight away They can proceed to inform your love
and you have been sent to exchange note To
place your order successfully A check on the
black and red book on your next Inside
left hand side Finally Which Protection
Question Security Decision and Projection
Page Views Exchange Segment Settlement Number
Amount You can see the details like date and
time with your amount used for buying or
selling stocks Debit from and credit to
your comment On Equity Security
Protection page you can see the details like
date and time of new stock debit
from and credit to your comment On this page
also displays the maximum sell quantity,
pure plot quantity and available
quantity and shades in the Buy Today and
Tomorrow column No details Place your order
and verified details You can also share
your  Portfolio for the details about you
talk to
polo gas updated on the plus one day
report police action give details like
percentage change in your stocks price
realized and unrealized profit and loss
reaction column give directions to buy or selves to talk
in your portfolio dial
100 2013 an option and checking for
production of new stock but plus science
give you all subscribe now amazon
subscribe back like subscribe news that
and watch heart and icici
cracked.com problems of investing
isko easy address.com hope you enjoyed
watching this medium lo